we're gonna practice Alliance dance as
much as we knew already vamos a
practicar la danse le on a stone a las
Palmas I'm going to just give you a
brief description of the the third
that's why I don't have a description of
the zero we're on a second
sorry second of the formulas right
estamos en el segundo nivel del mu del
Reino seem forma and I'll take you
through the whole thing again in order
okay let's go yeah sir
yo los voy a llevar por todo recorrido
and northern so don't worry but this
morning we'll go through everything
we've done so far
as you can see broke open recorded
Palomita soon a story so let me describe
it first and then we'll try to do it
together okay primero all boy yes Alison
my scripts Yanni local in tantrums and
Cervantes the first by the way the whole
thing is called the lion stance
Toula Lomita since IAM Aladdin's early
on we're starting in the desire realm
state of mind which is like tasting
cappuccino listening to air conditioner
ok empezamos an original de sel eskimo
provide cappuccino escuchar Elida
condicional then we're going to go you
know through the forum realm levels form
levels logo vamos a soui another 15,000
you lose the ring on a former focusing
on our heart and focus on El Corazon
which is still has a component of physic
physicalness
we're still aware of physicalness okay
yeah a stylist I won't say most
conscientious Ella physically dad then
we'll go into the formulas formulas for
formulas meditations okay
Ramos otra vez de la nación as the Ramos
informant and the first one we did
yesterday was called la primera
Christmas in the space okay and it's
that feeling of the body is anesthetized
okay the body is numb la primera
infinity s possum finito con el
sentimiento de Klerk or post anesthesia
no awareness of form seen don't LS
aparicio la conciencia la forma and then
we expand the mind as far as space and
you can keep going it's like if you drop
the stone in the middle of this leg and
then it would just keep going the the
Ripper would just keep going like that
okay Lourdes Panama lament hace el
espacio infinito como cuando Venter soon
appeared renewal hago la soon as
expansive 'as the Las Olas continued and
continued and continued and then the
second formless
oh by the way when you go from desire to
form you compare something to something
si en por cierto para cuando 2 passes
del rey no el deseo alrey no la forma lo
haces comparin de una cosa con una otra
there's this desire or I I don't want to
listen to the air-conditioner anymore I
want to go someplace more quiet
I am the Sarah knocker escuchar later
commissioner Herrera un lugar Moscow
so that's the basic idea between these
rounds okay
y esta es la vía Vasek Allah Tran
transition train and when you get to the
end of the forum yeah you are el final
de cuarto reign and final form your deep
into your heart
estas dentro de Corazon and your mind
feels how should I say even the feeling
of happiness is gone your mind just
feels how you go fat 9
the feelings are flatline
incluso ie tu mente esposa parisa el
sentimiento de la felicidad to maintain
and train una Mesa Tana Planitia the
young star snail and at the last part of
the forum your body is almost like
somebody gave it a shot like numb
anesthetized
okay you know parte de la forma to
corpore astonished SEL como sisters
Anastasio
then you compare that body that physical
heart
- no no no physical logo en la siento
transition compare us as a corp of
physical as a Corazon physical and/or
you can always so it's another
transition because you're comparing
where you are with where you could go
that's why you move from the formula to
the formula y de la manera comment
Moreno la forma else in forma is compare
ando una cosa con la otra la physically
reconnaissance ela physically like even
this numb body is to growth and I want
to go somewhere more subtle later ask a
stochastic where por este carpod el
costo consider Corazon as demasiado
vents Akira Yamaoka mucho mass appeal
and the difference between the first
formulas meditation and the second
formulas meditation is again a
comparison
ilari Forenza entre el primer nivel de
reims informal el segundo knee well as
the transition the never sought
recuperación the feeling in the first
formless realm for me it's like as I
said I feel horizontal I feel like a
lake the top of a lake and my mind is
just going out in a ripple and it's not
going to stop it's still going
el sentimiento para mean el primero
nivel de de la maison forma es como es
horizontal is common lago y case
expanded by panocha parada expand
edition then in the second form a
theorem okay that's where we are this
morning en el segundo nivel de reims
informa i'm going to take away the image
of forum and I'm just gonna think about
the state of mind that's writing that
image going on you see drop everything
just think consciousness consciousness
going like this not not some kind of
image of a lake or space okay
in when you go from the first formless
realm to the second formless realm it's
because you're dissatisfied with space
and you want something more subtle and
that consciousness okay sella transition
del espacio finito not known that expand
this allah concerns infinita to
plataforma be swallow imaginative ah de
expansion podría ser logic as expanded
para to discuss and 15 satisfied shock
on also plataforma Concha visually that
case my way he entrar en estado
inclusive masa till he was popularly
mocking cassia so la conciencia concerns
expansive seen libretto visual mental
canal walls expand via okay got it
before you drop the air conditioner
because it was too gross and you wanted
something more subtle which was your
heartbeat
primero a landowner on larrikin senado
port era muy bien so tyrion algo mas
utility old Corazon and now you're it
gets very subtle okay just a motion you
are dropping the image of endless space
because
endless consciousness is more cool more
sub
general imagine del espacio infinito la
stessa bondo Nando por que la conciencia
infinita a mucho mejor mucho mas appear
and again it would take about an hour to
make this transition
yes sir esta transition to Maria kimono
aura so we're gonna pretend I see que
vamos a fin here we're gonna visualize
we are moving from first formulas to
second formulas but actually we're
halfway in the air conditioner still a
visa lease our customizations la
transition the Brimmer nivel del station
for telling us in forma El Segundo nivel
peaceful Sally Machine are no pero con
generally estaremos
an entire conditional are these levels
ago a castle stores novellas me that he
was so Luna meta no okay don't get
distracted
nice try again don't spend all your time
looking at the car at the airport when
you could be riding home in Susanna's
cars here poor cannot Olivia no lot o en
el aeropuerto commodious era to Casa de
notre susana so why are we why are we
practicing them for the pork estamos
practicals does make the Sienese it's
like if you are an iron woman in in a
colorado competition eskimo Sierra she
won competition yes
Allegan hola competition iron man primer
lugar en border Colorado in current as a
goalkeeper anyway so you run in a lot of
crazy places if you want to run in a
normal place you seen I mean you run up
and down big mountains if the race is
going to be held on a small mountainous
okay si para hacer Tantra Nami ento para
ganar en su
orefici a normal penis ks7 tournament
and east into lugar Eskimo Montana's
Escalera Jesse
so just for training purposes solo part
efectos and train onion to me maybe you
run up and down this mountain here even
though you're gonna run a flat race in
Colorado is enemy solo para factors para
tener oh man entrada en toe suba suba
face en esta Montana pero cuando la
carrera sabah sura in colorado hacer una
superficie plan there's a second purpose
to practice this can you guess what also
in the purpose it todas estas prácticas
he says seed seizes okay ELISA samia's
what a negative purpose
call Estella factor negative oh now you
don't mistake it for emptiness you see
what I mean you don't go there by
accident one day and you say oh I saw
emptiness a lot ro propósito testamento
seoane asperity not to come fund us no
confundus s aztecs perience second a
perception director la cuidad Silvia
poor accident ain't rasayan esta
estimated Evo say Paz canastas perceive
in new directamente lava quia or you go
to some teaching and the teacher
describes
form round number three and you're like
and they call it emptiness possum Nancy
Nancy el maestro catalyst a party endo
described a personal trainers in forma
de caso Slovak we da / - yeah service
que no lo es porque la pray mr. king ten
year then you know you can say oh yeah I
tried that I know what it is our teacher
took us there and that's not emptiness
that's just that's just a car a fancy
car
he totally took quest and Sciences
yah-yah-yah premier so maestro maestro
Nolan sin oh yes oh no as the perception
directed avocadoes implemented and we
could look at the year I am and I think
if if you practice these nine right ten
it's gonna be ten is used as practical
as doesn't know if I can really run a
service and then you go to meditation
classes by anybody you look over analyst
classes and meet the sea only called
Kirika Allison Sonya what you hear will
be in in one of those ten lessons
enhances guess Cochin mr. Bannister in
carnitine argon SSDs so some copper
starts out his summary by saying new
moon changes something so Kappa M pieces
so resuming what it mean yeah these
states of meditation are are still
negative states of mind there are still
linked number one this occurs closest
Australis there minute ASEAN C&C endo
nihilism limitation estas mentalis
negative OHS Castle vinculin marrow you
know the linger on SIA not what a la
vida so it if you practice them a
specialist but beacon then you can then
if you go to some weird meditation class
and they talked for a long time about
something you can you can in your of
course it's not polite to say that's
just stupid mistake number three you
know see well now Atlas ami
many TAS yawn and to mantilla Northwest
Aesir pero cuando switches like classes
a CSL roar
numero tres yeah Lopez clasificado not
super serious ask is in the road but at
least yourself you won't you won't be
attracted to just doing that yeah
para por lo menos to yet
la enseñanza note S&P rasa Trudeau a
soul Viserys